1. [Home](https://logicdir.com/)
2. [Pages](https://logicdir.com/pages)
3. Page

Privacy Policy
==============

Print

Created on 1 March, 2023 | 2,227 views | 1 minutes read

The privacy policy explains what personal information we collect and how it is used. The Site collects this information to analyze and provide better experiences with our services. If you do not want to agree to the Privacy Policy, you must not access or u

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy policy explains what personal information we collect and how it is used. The Site collects this information to analyze and provide better experiences with our services. If you do not want to agree to the Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the Site.

**Information collected**

The Site may collect personal information, such as your email address, when you use the contact form or sign up for our services.

**Use of information**

We use your personal information to provide and improve our services, including content personalization and data analytics. In addition, we can contact you to send updates about our services or to answer questions or comments.

**Information sharing**

We do not sell or share your personal information with third parties, except as necessary to provide our services or as required by law.

**Security**

We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, theft or unauthorized use. However, we cannot guarantee that your information is completely secure.

**Updating information**

To request an update or fix on a shortened URL you create, go to the contact form and enter the long URL and short URL you want to change.

**Privacy rights**

LogicDir may send messages to advertise a product or service, and you may choose not to receive marketing messages by unsubscribing from our list.

**Cookies and advertising network**

We may use third-party advertising companies to display ads when you visit our Site. These companies, may use cookies which are small text files placed on your device and similar technologies to collect information for the purpose of displaying ads related to products and services of interest to you.

LogicDir may display advertisements served by advertising companies, which uses cookies to identify user preferences and browsing habits. Users can get more information about these cookies and privacy on advertising companies's websites.

Web browsers accept cookies automatically, but if you prefer you can modify the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our Site and other sites on the Internet.

**Privacy policy changes**

We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. Any changes will be posted on this page and will take effect immediately.

**Other important information**

If there are any questions regarding privacy or need any further information, please contact our team.

Updated on 9 March, 2023

Copyright © 2024 LogicDir.

Light Dark
